Semanur Çelebi, Frontend Developer

Rotterdam, Netherlands, 0627906036, semanur.celebi@outlook.com

LINKS	Linkedin, Github		
PROFILE	Developed my skills as a Front-End Developer at an e-commerce website, gaining valuable experience with Vue.js and JavaScript over the past 2 years. Actively participated in updating older projects to new technologies and successfully translated design concepts into functional code. Contributed to improving the user experience by providing my comments on the design of some projects. Outside of work, Organize weekly board game nights, honing my strategic thinking and collaboration abilities.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Dec 2023 — Present	Freelance Frontend Developer	, Tellpal	Rotterdam, Netherlands
	 Tellpal is an application where children can listen to stories through a mobile app. Created a website based on the provided designs to promote the application, resulting in an in to 20% in the download rate of the app. Additionally, I supported the creation of a user-friendly website by sharing my experiences in 		
Jan 2022 — Jul 2023	Frontend Developer, Beymen	Group	İstanbul, Turkey
	 Created from scratch an employee performance evaluation project in the Beymen Group to improve operational efficiency. With this project, the performances of almost 50 developers working in the company began to be monitored through the website instead of Excel. Played a key role in the development of the Beymen e-commerce website, focusing on improvements in the cart, order, and payment functionalities, which resulted in a 15% increase in overall checkout completion rates in one year. Migrated the given designs to the project using Figma and Zeplin. Took part in migrating projects written with Jquery to Vue2. Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues. Estimated work hours and tracked progress using Scrum methodology. 		
Jul 2021 — Dec 2021	Software Engineer Intern, Onftech Software Solutions İstanbul, Turkey		
	 Contributed to a Human Resources project developed from scratch using React and TypeScript, resulting in a 10% decrease in processing time for HR tasks. Written backend code in C# and prepared SQL queries as needed. 		
EDUCATION			
Sep 2017 — Mar 2022	Software Engineering, Karade	niz Technical University	Trabzon, Turkey
HARD SKILLS	Vue	CSS/SCSS	
	React	Figma	
	TypeScript	Zeplin	
	JavaScript	Git	
	RestApi	Jira	
	HTML	Scrum	
PASSIONS	Board Game		
	Volleyball		
	Reading - Mainly Detective		
	Anime		
	- t.		

Traveling